https://www.kcstarlight.com/privacy-policy/

This symbol links to our search site page.
CLOSE
This symbol links to our search site page.
Privacy Policy
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE STARLIGHT THETARE WEBSITE (“Website”). FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION PLEASE REVIEW STARLIGHT FAQS.
General Overview
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.
Starlight Theatre is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to facilitate commercial transactions and to provide you with a more personalized experience. We have created this Privacy Policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of all of our customers and visitors. The following Privacy Statement discloses the information-gathering and dissemination practices and policies of the Starlight Theatre.
Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. For some services, we either collect or transfer personal information to a service provider you have selected, or you may visit other merchants through links on our site who may collect and use your personal information. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others.
This Website is managed by Starlight Theatre a private 501(c)(3) non-profit organization.
Types of information that may be collected
The personally identifiable information we collect is used to facilitate delivery of products and/or services to our customers. In the process of providing these products and/or services, we require our customers to provide certain personally identifiable information. Specific details may include, but is not limited to the following and may be subject to change:
In the case of contests, promotions, and/or newsletter registrations: We require all users and/or customers wishing to participate in any of our contests, drawings, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters to complete a Participant Registration Form. During this registration process we generate and collect certain personally identifiable information.
The personally identifiable information that may be collected from our customers in completion of a registration form: Customer’s first name, last name, zip code, phone number, age and email address. Winners of contests, drawings, sweepstakes, and/or promotions will be required to provide additional personally identifiable information such as a shipping address and telephone number.
In the case of product and/or service purchases: In order to complete the purchase of a product and/or service, an online credit card transaction is required. During this process we generate and collect certain verifiable personally identifiable information.
The verifiable personally identifiable information required includes the customer’s first and last name, first and last name of the credit card owner, credit card billing address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, customer’s shipping address, phone number, and email address.
If a customer sends us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.
Personally identifiable information does not include aggregated information that is not linked to any of your personally identifiable information. Such aggregated information may be shared with our marketing partners, advertisers and others.
How is information collected?
We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:
Registration
You may be asked first to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, including, but not limited to, Newsletters, Contests, Forums, Fantasy or other subscription based services.
Newsletters and Website Emails
Starlight Theatre may offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Website, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our business partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Website. You may cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided in the designated area of newsletters or emails.
Contests or Sweepstakes
Starlight Theatre may operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website, which may require registration. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes. We may ask your permission to allow us to post publicly some of your information on the Website, such as on a winner’s page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes, except as required by applicable law, we will not post your information without your permission. In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Website, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we have no control over the information collected and accordingly urge you to review the advertiser’s or sponsor’s privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.
Surveys or Voting
From time-to-time Starlight Theatre may request personally identifiable information from you via surveys or voting polls. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.
Cookies
As with many Websites, the Website uses standard technology called "cookies," which are small data files that are transferred to your computer when you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your Web browser to the Website whenever you visit the Website, and make using the Website easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Website. Cookies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you generally can opt out of providing this information by turning the cookies off in your browser; however, some areas of the Website may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.
IP Addresses and Click-stream Data
We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Our computers identify your computer by its IP address. When you request Web pages from the Website, our computers log your IP address.
Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.
Transaction Information
If you order any information from our Website, buy any of our products or subscribe for any of the services offered on our Website, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including financial information such as a credit card number and expiration date and general contact, billing and shipping information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. Such information is collected and stored through encrypted means for your protection.
How we use the information we collect
We internally use personally identifiable information about our customers to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site’s content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and provide better service to our customers.
We may occasionally use a customer’s email address and, in rare situations mailing address or phone number, to contact a customer regarding administrative matters or notices.
We may use information in the file we maintain about a customer to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.
With whom the information may be shared
Information we collect may be accessed by a variety of parties, depending upon the project for which the information was originally collected, the terms of that engagement, and the policies into or out of which the consumer has opted. From time to time, we may send you offers from Starlight Theatre, and our promotional partners based on the information you have provided us. In addition, we may provide information we collect about you with third party companies regarding promotions, sweepstakes and other opportunities/offers. These third parties are subject to stringent data security and confidentiality requirements.
We may be required to collect, share or disclose your personal identifiable information without your consent in the following instances: i) pursuant to judicial orders, subpoenas, decrees, or warrants; ii) in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, safety or the security of persons or property, violations of the Starlight Theatre Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use, or as otherwise authorized or required by law; and iii) in connection with the sale or transfer of any ownership interest in Starlight Theatre.
While we believe this disclosure of your information will result in opportunities that may be of interest to you, you have the right to tell us not to give your information to any third party (except as noted above). If you want Starlight Theatre to keep all of your information we have collected confidential and not share it with any third party (except as noted above), please either email us or mail your written request to:
Starlight Theatre
4600 Starlight Road
Kansas City, Mo 64132
Your request must include your name, email address, mailing address and must be signed. (Signature only required for written request sent by regular mail). Please allow six weeks to process your request. After your request has been fulfilled, the only disclosures we will make are those required by law.
What choices do I have about Starlight Theatre collecting, using, and sharing my information?
It is possible for you to use much of our site without giving us any personally identifiable information. You can request at any time that Starlight Theatre not send future e-mail to you either by unsubscribing from the communication or by contacting us. Also, as mentioned above, there are ways to limit the information collected through technology -- though some of our features won’t work if you decide to do this.
What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?
We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. However, please keep in mind that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet and/or the World Wide Web.
Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards
The Website may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. Starlight Theatre cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.
Links to other websites
You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other sites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a sponsor logo, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different website. This includes links from social networks, sponsors and partners that may use the Website’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that website’s privacy policy before providing any personal information.
A special note for parents concerning privacy
We do not encourage children to participate in providing us with any personally identifiable information. We ask that children (12 years of age and under) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor under the age of 13 years, please use our services only under the approval and supervision of your parents or legal guardian(s).
We support the guidelines and regulatory requirements provided in the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm
Limitation of Liability
By providing us with any personal information you expressly and unconditionally release and hold harmless Starlight Theatre, and their subsidiaries, affiliates, directors, officers, employees and agents from any and all liability for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected personal information. In addition, while Starlight Theatre takes efforts to ensure the proper and appropriate use of data provided by Starlight Theatre to third party companies, promotional partners or vendors, Starlight Theatre is not liable for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected personal information by Starlight Theatre or the above-mentioned entities.
Notification of changes and acceptance of the Privacy Policy
By using this Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. Starlight Theatre may change this policy from time to time. If so, any such changes will be posted on this page, so that Starlight Theatre may keep its users informed of its information collection practices. Accordingly, we recommend that you consult this page frequently so that you are aware of our latest policy. Your continued use of the Website shall constitute your acceptance of such revised privacy policy.
Event Listing
Ticket Offers
Season Tickets
Plan Your Visit
Gift Certificates
Read Our Blog
Accessibility Info
Donate
Retrieving performance data.
Please wait.
This may take a few moments.
Error
There was an error loading the select your own seat.
